(サクラ)ホントなの？
ナルトが三尾の中にいるって。
Is it true...?
Naruto... is inside the Three-Tails?
(カブト)フン。
あのはしゃぎよう まるでガキだね。
(濡羅吏)キャハハハッ
なんか気分いいじゃない。
(鬼霧)ああ 今までの
オレじゃねえみてえだ。
Huh!
They're so excited...
just like a kid...
(鬼鳳)
これまでの疲れが吹っ飛んでる。
いや それだけじゃねえ。
なんか こう力がみなぎるっての。
I feel so happy.
Yeah, almost like it's not me.
いいかい なんとしても木ノ葉の
連中から 幽鬼丸を取り返すんだ。
My fatigue's completely gone.
Not only that...
ウフフフッ 心配症ね メガネ君。
It's as though I'm filled with strength...
今なら誰にも負ける気がしねえ。
Listen, we've got to get
Yuukimaru away from the Leaf,
例え 紅蓮にだってな！
no matter what it takes.
《フッ せいぜい活躍してくれよ。
まあ 期待してないけどね》
You worry too much, Four-Eyes.
Right now,
I feel like I can't lose to anyone!
Not even Guren!
(カカシ)その話 ホントなのか？
Do what you can.
Not that I'm expecting much...
この子が 幽鬼丸が言うには➡
紅蓮て晶遁使いは生きてるって。
(ヤマト)ナルトもその紅蓮と一緒に
三尾に飲み込まれたと言うんだね。
Is that story true?
According to this child, Yuukimaru,
(カカシ)これだけ捜しても
見つからないということは➡
Guren the Crystal Style User is alive...
その話は
まんざらウソでもなさそうだな。
He says that she and Naruto
were swallowed by the Three-Tails.
だが なぜ紅蓮が無事だとわかる？
The fact that we've searched this much
and still haven't found him means
(幽鬼丸)これは
紅蓮さんが作ってくれた。
that story may have
some truth to it...
紅蓮さんに何かあれば
これも壊れちゃう。
But how do you know
that Guren is okay?
なるほどね。
Guren-san made this for me.
(シズネ)でも それは紅蓮が
無事である証拠であって➡
If something happens to her
this will break, as well...
ナルト君が 無事でいると
いうことにはならないわ。
I see.
確かに 三尾の腹の中が
どうなってるかは➡
That's proof that Guren is okay,
誰にもわからない。
(キバ)例え 無事だったとしても➡
but it doesn't mean that Naruto is okay.
ナルトと晶遁野郎は 一緒なんだろ？
That's true.
No one knows what the inside
of the Three-Tails' stomach is like.
すでに２人でやりあって 決着が
ついてるってこともあるぜ。
Even if he is okay, Naruto is
with that Crystal user, right?
それじゃ ナルトは…。
今 そんな仮定は無意味だね。
It's possible that the two
have already fought each other
生きてることを信じ
まずは三尾を探さないと。
and settled things.
Then Naruto is...
ボク 探してみる。
Right now, those assumptions
are meaningless.
We need to believe he's still alive
and find the Three-Tails first.
探せるのか？ 三尾を。
うん。 はっきりとは
わからないんだけど 感じるんだ。
I'll... look for it...
Can you find it? The Three-Tails...
でも 三尾を発見して
それからどうすんだよ。
Yes... I don't know for sure...
but I sense it...
もう一度 封印術を行うわ。
But what'll we do after
we find the Three-Tails?
よし その間にナルトの救出を試そう。
I'll seal it once more.
三尾が暴れた場合に備え ヤマト。
All right. We'll try to rescue Naruto
while you're doing that.
ナルトと一緒に 紅蓮が
発見されたときのために➡
シノにも同行してもらう。
In the event the Three-Tails
becomes violent,
Yamato, let's have Shino go with you
just in case we find Guren with Naruto.
サイは 上空で待機。
残りは あたりの
警戒にあたってもらう。
Sai, you stand by up above
in the sky.
The rest of you will guard
the surrounding area.
あのカブトが相手だ。
何を仕掛けてくるか。
ナルトを頼むぜ。
(シノ)ああ。
sha la la some day in the future
sha la la itsuka kitto
お前たちも気をつけろ。
(カカシ)シノ！
I will for sure hold it in my hand
boku wa te ni suru nda
そろそろ出してくれ。
わかった。
it will softly set ablaze
hakanaki mune ni sotto
a light in my empty heart
hikari moeteyuke
さぁ みんな。
私たち封印班は
隊の最後尾から➡
三尾を刺激しないように
静かに進むわよ。
(３人)はい！
the "impulses" that makes you want to meet it
aitaku naru no shoudou
(ヒナタ)ナルト君…。
the "innocence" that makes you want to cry
nakitaku naru no junjou
they've gone into the summer fire
natsu no hi ni tobikonda
the fireflies aren't coming back
hotaru wa kaeranai
you didn't say a single word and left a kiss for me behind
anata wa nanimo iwazu kuchizuke wo nokoshite
and nodded as you still got burned
kitsuzuku mama unazuita ne
it was so sad that my life was wavering
kanashii hodo inochi yurameiteita
sha la la some day in the future
sha la la itsuka kitto
I will for sure hold it in my hand
boku wa te ni suru nda
it will softly set ablaze
hakanaki mune ni sotto
a light in my empty heart
hikari moeteyuke
sha la la my sweet lovely dear
sha la la itoshiki hito
I can also see you right now
anata mo mieteiru no
the dazzling moon will softly
mabayui tsuki ga sotto
illuminate the morning day
ashita wo terashite
and strongly and strongly shine on
tsuyoku tsuyoku kagayaite
Guidepost of the
Camellia
We're up against Kabuto...
no telling what he might do.
Look after Naruto.
Right...
You guys be careful, too.
Shino!
Let's get going.
Understood.
Okay, everyone!
We're the Sealing Team.
Let's move quietly from the very back,
so we don't excite the Three-Tails, okay?
-Right!
Naruto-kun...
(ナルト)んっ!?
うわっ！
うわっ… だぁ！
ゲッ!!
ギャーッ!!
だぁ～っ!!
(紅蓮)どうした？
クッ！ やられたな。
What's the matter?
影分身が 全部。
なんだと!?
They've been attacked...
every one of my clones.
What...?
この音は… ヤツらだ！
That sound... It's them.
やばいぞ この数は！
クッ！
This is bad. We're outnumbered...
なんだ？
What...?
ゲッ！ あんなでけえのも
いんのかよ!?
There was one that huge, too?!
やるしかない。
って そんな体で
お前 戦えんのかよ!?
No choice but to fight.
Can you fight in your condition?!
どこに逃げ場がある!?
Then where's a way to escape?!
確かにねえけどよ。
You're right, there isn't one.
晶遁 六角手裏剣！
Crystal Style: Hexagonal Shuriken!
クッ！
ほらみろ！
You see! No effect at all.
全然 効かねえじゃねえか！
ここは オレがおとりになっから➡
I'll be the decoy, so run when
you get the chance, okay?!
隙をみて逃げろ いいな!?
いくぜ！
Here I go!
チッ！ どりゃ～!!
うわっ！ ぐっ！
くっ…！
ヘッ… ん!?
くらえ～!!
Take this!
Guren!
紅蓮！
ヘッ どうだ！
Heh! How do you like that?!
あっ!?
-Are you all right?
-Uh... yeah.
大丈夫か!?
あ ああ。
うっ うぅ…。
クソッ！
Damn... Shadow Clone Jutsu!
影分身の術！
Get on my back right now!
早く オレにおぶされ！
そ そんなことできるか！
I can't do that!
Why not?!
Because... my... pride...
なんでだよ!?
それは…。
Fool! This is no time for
troublesome talk like that!
私の プライドが…。
バカか!!
んな めんどくせえこと
言ってる場合じゃねえだろ!!
Put me down, you nimrod!
あっ… バ バカ！ おろせ！
Stay still!
じっとしてろ！
Hurry up!
Right!
早くしろ！
おう！
とりゃ～っ!!
Yes!
よっしゃ!!
わ～っ！
だ～っ！
I wonder if things are going all right
for Sakura and the others.
(テンテン)うまくいってるかな？
サクラたち。
That's if Naruto is okay.
ナルトが無事ならの話だけどよ。
Of course he's okay.
(リー)大丈夫 無事に決まってます。
彼は ボクが一度は➡
Because he's the person
I want to have an all-out match
with one day.
本気で手合わせをしたいと
思ってる人ですから！
What is it, Akamaru?
Seems our enemy is
making its appearance.
どうした？ 赤丸。
Good timing.
I was just getting fired up!
どうやら
敵さんのお出ましのようだぜ。
ちょうどいいです。
気分が高ぶってきたところです。
I'll show how I feel for Naruto
with my fists!
ナルト君への思いを
この拳に込めて…。
でやっ!!
You people again?!
You knew it was us?
You can hide your shape and smell,
but you can't hide your bloodthirstiness.
また あなたたちですか。
よく わかったな。
I won't lose to an opponent
I've beaten once before!
たとえ 姿やニオイを消しても
その殺気は消せません。
Don't underestimate us.
一度 勝った相手には
負けませんよ。
We're not the same as we were before!
甘くみるなよ。 オレたちは
以前のオレたちじゃねえぜ。
Dark Smoke Sphere!
We can't get near them... like this.
魔煙丸！
We won't lose
in the barrage of grenades!
これでは 近づけない…。
You are so naïve...
弾数なら負けないわ！
甘いわよ。
My Kunai...
Appear! Smoke Dragon!
私のクナイが…。
現れろ 煙龍！
What's the matter?
They're here... under us...
あっ…。
どうした？
Okay. Sealing Team, get ready!
Wait...
いる。 この下に。
There's no way out.
Guren-san and Naruto are
looking for a way out.
よし 封印班。 準備を。
(幽鬼丸)待って。
A way out?
If we open up a hole from the outside,
that'll be their way out.
出口がないんだ。
紅蓮さんたちは 出口を探してる。
What's going on?
First, we'll have to see what's
at the bottom of the lake.
Camellias...
Bring me a lot of camellia blossoms...
Camellias?
Why did you save me?
That was my line!
Because if you died now,
there was no way I could survive.
What? You're relying on me?
Hey, how is your wound?
Don't touch me!
Once we're out of here,
you and I are enemies!
Suit yourself.
But I'm not handing over Yuukimaru.
Why're you so protective of Yuukimaru?
I told you before.
Regardless of your reasons for
your loyalty to Orochimaru,
he is evil.
He's probably using you.
Like him.
出口？
外から穴を開けられれば
きっと そこが出口になるよ。
Him?
At any rate, where you
and Orochimaru are;
いったい どういうこと？
that's absolutely not the place
for Yuukimaru to return to.
まあ まずは 湖底を
調べてみる必要がありそうだね。
I'll go and take a quick look up ahead.
(幽鬼丸)椿…。
Since my clones can't do surveillance.
椿の花を たくさん持ってきて！
椿？
なぜ 私を助けた？
それは こっちのセリフだ。
どうして オレを助けたんだ？
Damn... this looks really deep...
今 お前に死なれては
どうあがいても助からない。
Guess we have no choice.
なんだよ… オレのこと
頼りにしてんじゃん。
おい 傷口は どうだ？
Fog...?
触るな！ ここから出れば
お前と私は 敵同士だ。
This is bad!
勝手にしろ。
けど 幽鬼丸は渡さねえぞ。
Is it them again?!
What?!
どうして そんなに
幽鬼丸にこだわる？
前にも言っただろ。
どんな事情があろうと➡
Hey, who's there?!
What're you doing...?
お前が くっついてる
大蛇丸ってヤツは悪党だ。
It can't be...
どうせ お前も利用されてんだよ。
アイツみてえに…。
Sasuke! What're you doing here?
アイツ？
とにかく➡
お前や大蛇丸がいる場所が
帰る場所なんて➡
そんなことは 絶対にねえ。
ちょっくら
この先を見てくるってばよ。
影分身じゃ
偵察にならないからな。
Stop it, Sasuke!
I have something to tell you!
クソッ… ずいぶん深そうだな。
Stop it!
Sasuke!
しかたねえ！
霧？ まずい！
This is the Three-Tails' fog...
I see...
また アイツらか！
あっ!?
This fog shows illusions of
the weakness in the souls
おい！ 誰だ!?
なんで こんなところに！
of the people who stand
within in it...
If I stand inside it,
I will have to face them, as well...
ウソだろ…。
Sasuke, stop it!
サスケ！ なんで お前が
ここにいるんだ!?
あっ!?
やめろ！ サスケ！
オレは お前に伝えたいことが
あるんだ！
やめろ！ サスケ!!
あっ！
You're...!
これは 三尾の霧。
そうか！
I've...
I've done something to you
that I can never make amends for...
I want you to forgive me...
《この霧は 中にいる人間の
心の弱さを➡
Even if it's meaningless now,
I will protect your child to the end,
even if it costs me my life!
幻覚にして見せるのか…。
中に入れば 私も
それに向かい合うことになる》
サスケ やめろ！
あっ！ くっ…！
うぅ… あっ！ うっ…。
Sasuke...
You have a place to return to!
Did you forget about that?!
Listen, Sasuke!
Let go! Let go of me!
Pull yourself together, Naruto!
あなたは！
What you're seeing is an illusion!
あなたに
取り返しのつかないことを…。
(紅蓮)許してほしい…。
それは 今さら無意味だとしても➡
あなたの子供は
たとえ私の命にかえても➡
What?
守り抜いてみせる！
You saved me.
You saw Uchiha Sasuke?
Yeah...
You know Sasuke?
うっ!? がっ！
I met him at Orochimaru-sama's place.
He's a scary guy.
Is he okay?
サスケ… お前には
帰る場所があんだろ！
Is he doing well?
Uh, yeah... Why do you ask?
それを忘れちまったのかよ！
Isn't it obvious?!
なあ！ サスケ！
He's one of us!
I have to bring him back and
うっ… ぐっ！
tell Sasuke that he has
a place to return to!
離せ！ 離しやがれ！
You... Are you seriously intending
to bring Sasuke back?
しっかりしろ ナルト
お前が見てるのは 幻覚だ。
Of course!
助かったぜ。
That...
うちはサスケに会ったのか？
ああ。
ん？ お前
サスケを知ってんのか。
Sasuke...?
This guy must be a real fool.
大蛇丸様のところで会った
恐ろしいヤツだ。
Of all the crazy things,
he wants to save Sasuke...?
アイツは無事でいんのか？
元気でいるのか？
ああ
なんで そんなことを聞く？
What's so funny?
決まってんだろ
アイツは オレたちの仲間なんだ。
I've never met such a fool!
What brought that out of the blue?
必ず アイツを連れ戻して➡
You're splitting my sides! Really...
サスケに 帰るべき場所があるって
伝えなきゃなんねえ。
Hey, are you all right?!
お前 本気で うちはサスケを
取り戻す気なのか？
当たり前だ！
あの…。
So that's the entrance to
the dimension Yuukimaru mentioned.
うちはサスケを？
If we tear that membrane,
we'd create a way out...
《コイツは ホントのバカか？
こともあろうに あのサスケまで
助けようというのか》
Now!
フフフ アハハハハハハ！
何がおかしいんだよ？
Lightning Blade!
お前みたいなバカには
会ったことがないよ。
What? The fog lifted...
Could it be flowing outside?
なんだよ 急に！
こりゃ 片腹痛い。
あ… ホントに痛い。
おい 大丈夫か？
Wha--?! When did they...?!
Now there's no way to escape.
Damn! Not again...!
They sure are persistent!
One more strike!
《なるほど あれが
幽鬼丸の言う異空間への入り口》
Come back, Naruto!
《あの膜を破ってやれば
出口ができるってわけか》
We're ready!
Let's do it now!
《今だ！》
《雷切！》
なんだ？ 霧がどこかに…。
まさか 外に流れてるのか。
いつの間に!?
これじゃ 逃げ場がない。
Naruto, there's something I have to tell you.
クソッ またかよ。
What is it?
This isn't a good time.
しつこいヤツらだってばよ。
Remember I told you that
Yuukimaru's mother is dead?
《もう一撃》
Yeah.
I'm the one... who killed her.
《帰ってこい ナルト！》
What did you just say?
At the time, Orochimaru-sama was
trying to build the Sound Village.
I attacked Yuukimaru's village
on his orders.
準備オッケーだ。
But I collapsed there after
exhausting my powers.
今だよ。
ナルト お前に言っておかなければ
ならないことがある。
何だってばよ こんなときに。
幽鬼丸の母親は
死んでると言ったな。
ああ。
殺したのは私だ。
That woman...
saved my life,
even though I was her enemy.
なんだって!?
あのとき➡
音の里を作ろうとしていた
大蛇丸様の命令で➡
Get away...
I'll close my eyes to this if you go now.
私は 幽鬼丸の里を襲った。
でも 力を使い果たした私は
その場に倒れてしまった。
Are you planning to betray me, Guren?
(紅蓮)あの人は
敵である私を助けてくれた。
But...
I... I...
((逃げろ 今なら 目をつぶる！
Out of my desire to be accepted
by Orochimaru-sama...
I killed her...
I had sealed away the memories
and emotions of that moment.
(大蛇丸)私を 裏切る気？ 紅蓮))
But when I met Yuukimaru,
they all came back to me.
なのに 私は… 私は…。
Is that why you protect Yuukimaru...?
As you said...
大蛇丸様に認められたい一心で
あの人を。
I hurt Yuukimaru's soul in a way
that I could never make amends.
I have no right to protect him...
Guren...
It's over for me!
But I will protect you
even if it costs me my life!
You must survive!
Please look after Yuukimaru.
私は あのときの記憶と感情を
自ら封印した。
It's weird hearing that from you!
Whatever happened in the past,
you're different now!
それが 幽鬼丸に会って
すべて思い出した。
You...
それで 幽鬼丸は？
お前の言うとおりだ。
Camellia?
幽鬼丸に取り返しのつかない
心の傷を負わせた私に➡
あの子を守る資格なんてない。
紅蓮。
私は もうダメだ。
でも ここは私の命に代えても
お前を守る！
Yuukimaru...?
必ず 生き延びてくれ。
幽鬼丸を 頼む。
He's trying to show us the way out!
んなこと言われても
気持悪いんだよ。
Look out!
昔 何があろうと
今のお前は違うんだろ？
お前…。
椿？
Okay, now!
♪♪(草笛)
I won't let you die in place like this!
We're going back together!
幽鬼丸。
アイツが オレたちに出口を
教えようとしてくれてんだ！
危ねえ！
(２人)うわ！
♪♪(草笛)
よし 今だ！
before the reality of a deep breath
sonzai to shinkokyuu no genjitsu wo mae ni
my gaze my very existence tries to challenge it
idomou to suru shisen wa
うわ！
mistakes are made and in the confusion of it all everything burns into my mind
machigai mo tomadoi mo zenbu yaki tsukeru
こんなとこで
お前を くたばらせたりはしねえ。
オレたちは
一緒に帰るんだってばよ！
in a series of moments
isshun no renzoku no naka de
beyond a great number of promises
ikutsu mono yakusoku no sono ue ni tatte wa
うわ～！
are the words that spilled over from the day as I reflect upon them
kamishimeru ano hi koboreochita kotoba
it's as though I made a vow which expresses these feelings into words
komerareta omoi wa chikai no you de
then it would link the befinning with the present day
kuchi ni sureba ima to hajimari wo tsunagu
it's not in my dreams
yume de wa nakute
that place doesn't exist in a fantasy world either
esoragoto no sekai de mo nai basho de sa
before the reality of a deep breath
sonzai to shinkokyuu no genjitsu no mae ni
my gaze my very existence tries to challenge it
idomou to suru shisen wa
mistakes are made and in the confusion of it all everything burns into my mind
machigai mo tomadoi mo zenbu yaki tsukete
embracing the long path ahead
sono zutto saki wo toraeru
in a series of moments
isshun no renzoku no naka de
え～ これから収録するシーンは➡
24時間以内に
敵のアジトに潜入するという➡
Next Episode
スリリングなシーンです。
マイク 届かねえな。
Oh no...
if anything went wrong and the Leaf
was able to seal the Three tails...
うわ！ あ…。
どうしたんだってばよ。
ヤマト隊長。
Orochimaru-sama's future strategy
would be forced to change dramatically.
台本が… ない。
ええ!?
また忘れたんですか？
I must prevent that.
これで ２回目ですよ！
ち 違うんだ ほら 今日は➡
Now that it's come to this,
I don't care if we lose Yuukimaru.
絶対に ミスの
許されないシーンだったでしょ。
だから 念入りに Ｖチェックをして…。
I'll use all of its power
to drive the Leaf out!
ちなみに Ｖチェックとは
画の入った映像を見ながら➡
Counterattack of
the Curse Mark
セリフの練習をすることよ。
Next time: "Counterattack of the Curse Mark"
言い訳ですか 木ノ葉の上忍も
落ちたものですね。
Uh, the next scene we're going
to shoot is a thrilling scene
あ あのね そうじゃなくて …。
in which you infiltrate the enemy's hideout
within 24 hours.
かっこ悪い。
(いの)見損なっちゃったな。
Huh? I can't reach the microphone.
そうだ そうだ。
もう そんなこと言わないで！
あ～。
しようがない オレの見せてやるよ。
What's the matter, Captain Yamato?
カカシ先輩！ って!!
I don't have... my script...
-What?!
-You forgot it again?
これ ボクのじゃないですか！
This is the second time.
あ？ そう？ 悪い悪い！
No, I didn't lose it.
Today's scene has to have
absolutely no mistakes, right?
(ヤマト)
しかも 変な落書き描いてるし！
もう かんべんしてくださいよ！
So I did a careful voice check...
For those who don't know,
a voice check is where
you rehearse your lines
as you watch a video with pictures.
Making excuses now?
The Leaf Jonin have sure fallen...
Uh... that's not what happened...
- That's uncool.
- I thought you were better than that.
I agree, I agree!
Come on, stop saying that...
Guess I'll just have to show you mine.
Kakashi-senpai...
This is mine!
Oh... it is?
Sorry, sorry.
What's more, there're all sorts
of odd doodles in here!
Oh..! Give me a break!